<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="data_list">
        <item> Plant a tree.</item>
        <item> Bake cookies for the neighbors or your family.</item>
        <item> Explore nature and go geocaching.</item>
        <item> Act out your childs favorite book.</item>
        <item> Make lanyard key chains.</item>
        <item> Visit an interactive museum.</item>
        <item> Have a catch in a local park or the backyard.</item>
        <item> Build an indoor tent or fort with couches and some bed sheets.</item>
        <item> Play Frisbee.</item>
        <item> Head to the local library.</item>
        <item> Turn on the radio and dance.</item>
        <item> Play Simon Says an oldie, but goodie.</item>
        <item> Dress up in last years Halloween costumes and have a have a costume parade.</item>
        <item> Put together a jigsaw puzzle.</item>
        <item> Create papier mch.</item>
        <item> Make homemade play dough.</item>
        <item> Follow a no-bake recipe.</item>
        <item> Play DIY bowling: Spray-paint two-liter bottles as makeshift bowling pins and use a handy soccer ball in place of a bowling ball.</item>
        <item> Plan a scavenger hunt.</item>
        <item> String together macaroni for jewelry.</item>
        <item> Host a picnic lunch   indoors or outdoors.</item>
        <item> Learn how to tie-dye T-shirts.</item>
        <item> Pull out the dress box, put on funny clothes and have a photo shoot.</item>
        <item> Head outdoors for bird watching.</item>
        <item> Create a time capsule.</item>
        <item> Write letters to soldiers .</item>
        <item> Play balloon volleyball.</item>
        <item> Have a potato-sack race.</item>
        <item> Arrange a Jenga tournament.</item>
        <item> Camp out in the backyard.</item>
        <item> Make up a secret handshake.</item>
        <item> Count how many times you can spin in a circle without getting dizzy.</item>
        <item> Make fruit kabobs.</item>
        <item> Create a smores station.</item>
        <item> Draw murals with sidewalk chalk.</item>
        <item> Play lily-pad leap with small rugs and towels strategically placed throughout the playroom or living room.</item>
        <item> Construct an indoor obstacle course.</item>
        <item> Choreograph a dance routine.</item>
        <item> Host a movie night. Plan for it by drawing tickets, making popcorn and setting up the room like a theater.</item>
        <item> Make bath fizzies  by combining citric acid, baking soda and cornstarch.</item>
        <item> Pull out some old socks and draw faces on them to make sock puppets   then put on a show.</item>
        <item> Play "Mother May I?".</item>
        <item> Make a friendship bracelet .</item>
        <item> Exercise those finger-painting skills.</item>
        <item> Pull out Twister.</item>
        <item> Practice saying the 50 states in alphabetical order</item>
        <item> Take silly pictures with a camera.</item>
        <item> Make up your own mad-libs.</item>
        <item> Host an at-home field day, complete with tug of war and team colors.</item>
        <item> Explore small areas of nature with a magnifying glass.</item>
        <item> Experiment with science. Make a papier mch volcano and mix baking soda and vinegar for an explosive reaction!</item>
        <item> Learn a new card game .</item>
        <item> Host a tea party.</item>
        <item> Partake in brainteasers, such as Sudoku, crossword puzzles and word searches.</item>
        <item> Set up the basketball game of HORSE or just shoot hoops.</item>
        <item> Teach kids to hula hoop.</item>
        <item> Jump rope.</item>
        <item> Go on a walk and let kids take pictures (with a disposable camera) of their favorite things around the neighborhood.</item>
        <item> Break out the pots and pans and practice drumming skills (ear plugs required for parents!).</item>
        <item> Rearrange your childs bedroom.</item>
        <item> Find and write to a pen pal.</item>
        <item> Mix homemade bubbles: 1 cup granulated soap or soap powder, 1 quart warm water, and liquid food coloring</item>
        <item> Make sandwiches and deliver them to a homeless shelter or the local food pantry.</item>
        <item> Set up a platter of new foods, maturing your tykes palette.</item>
        <item> Sew a pillow. Just grab some fabric, scissors, stuffing and a needle and thread.</item>
        <item> Play Hot Potato   use anything from a bean bag to a bar of soap.</item>
        <item> Explore the world with Google Maps    find your home, your childs school, favorite spots, etc.</item>
        <item> Name that tune.</item>
        <item> Ask "what do you want to be when you grow up" and then plan your day around that career. What would a fireman wear? What would a teacher do?</item>
        <item> Build an outdoor fort with tarps and bungees around trees.</item>
        <item> Make up a secret language.</item>
        <item> Phone a friend. Better yet, use Skype or FaceTime.</item>
        <item> Set up a make-your-own-sundae station.</item>
        <item> Host a watercolor night where everyone paints their favorite (fill-in-the-blank).</item>
        <item> Count and roll loose change lying around the house.</item>
        <item> Construct a family tree.</item>
        <item> Roller blade.</item>
        <item> Start a mini garden .</item>
        <item> Run through the sprinklers.</item>
        <item> Give the family pet a bath.</item>
        <item> Reminisce about your favorite family vacation and draw pictures of everything you did to make a book.</item>
        <item> Search for four-leaf clovers.</item>
        <item> Learn magic tricks.</item>
        <item> Run relay races.</item>
        <item> Make up a fun song about the family (My description is Jim and I like to swim, my sisters description is Cate and she likes to skate).</item>
        <item> Write a letter to someone special (Grandma, Santa, the Tooth Fairy, your childs favorite athlete, etc.) then mail it.</item>
        <item> Research popular constellations. At night, head outdoors to spot natures bountiful creations.</item>
        <item> Publish a pretend newspaper.</item>
        <item> Learn origami.</item>
        <item> Make a playdate with a friend.</item>
        <item> Try to replicate a famous painting.</item>
        <item> Learn the alphabet in Sign language.</item>
        <item> Have a lemonade stand.</item>
        <item> Pick flowers (from your own garden, of course) and create a flower arrangement for the dining room table.</item>
        <item> Practice cartwheels, somersaults and handstands in the backyard</item>
        <item> Memorize all 50 state capitals.</item>
        <item> Practice manners by pretending to go out to a fancy restaurant (at your own kitchen table).</item>
        <item> Construct a sun dial .</item>
        <item> Write a haiku poem.</item>
        <item> Make an eye-spy scavenger hunt (something shiny and blue, something round that makes noise, something clear, etc.).</item>
        <item> Head to the local farmers market and look for interesting products you have never seen before.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drawer_list">
        <item>My Favourites</item>
        <item>Rate Us</item>
        </string-array>
</resources>